Good evening. Welcome back.
S:晚上好. 欢迎回来.
Were you on a city tour today?
S:你们今天去市区观光了吗?
Did you go to the Public Gardens? And to Charles Street?
S:你们去公共花园了吗? 去查尔斯街(Charles Street)了吗?
Did you go to City Hall? And to ...
A:你们去市政厅(City Hall)了吗? 去了...
Oh, it was a big day.
D:Oh,是很精彩的一天.
First, we went down to the river.
D:首先, 我们去了河边.
Then we went to Paul Revere's house.
D:然后我们去了Paul Revere故居
We were at Bunker Hill.
D:我们去了Bunker Hill.
And then we went to Cambridge and Harvard.
D:然后我们去了剑桥和哈佛.
And then it was lunch, wasn't it?
D:然后是午餐, 不是吗?
You've been everywhere!
S:你们去了每个地方!
In the afternoon we went to the waterfront, across the South Shore..
D:下午时候我们去了码头(waterfront), 穿过了南海岸.
Didi, is there anywhere left to visit?
A:Didi, 还有任何剩余的地方吗?
Sure. Tomorrow we go wherever we want.
D:有的. 明天我们去任何我们想去的地方.
Paulo, where would you like to go next?
D:Paulo, 接下来你想去哪?
To my room, please. Just to my room!
P:去我的房间, 请. 只想去我的房间!